<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Priyanka</title>
    <link>/</link>
      <atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>Priyanka</description>
    <generator>Source Themes Academic (https://sourcethemes.com/academic/)</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 17 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <image>
      <url>/images/icon_hubc9621be2d9c7eb34fbb96ddfc2f8546_4058026_512x512_fill_lanczos_center_2.png</url>
      <title>Priyanka</title>
      <link>/</link>
    </image>
    
    <item>
      <title>Workshop Papers</title>
      <link>/workshop/workshop_paper/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/workshop/workshop_paper/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Synthesis with Explicit Dependencies</title>
      <link>/publication/date23/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/publication/date23/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Our paper on Synthesis with Explicit Dependencies has been accepted to &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.date-conference.com/&#34;&gt;DATE 2023&lt;/a&gt;. Moreover, it has also received the &lt;b&gt;best paper award nomination&lt;/b&gt;.&lt;br&gt;We present an approach that combines advances in machine learning with automated reasoning for efficiently synthesizing functions with explicit dependencies.&lt;br&gt;Joint work with: Subhajit Roy and Kuldeep S. Meel&lt;br&gt;</title>
      <link>/talk/16112022/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Nov 2022 14:15:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>/talk/16112022/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Excited to attend a fully packed &lt;a href = &#34;https://www.floc2022.org/&#34;&gt;FLoC-22&lt;/a&gt;. We will be presenting:&lt;br&gt; &lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;files/slides/qbf_workshop.pdf&#34;&gt; A data-driven approach for Boolean functional synthesis &lt;/a&gt; at QBF workshop. &lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;files/slides/dpcp.pdf&#34;&gt;Boolean functional synthesis and its applications &lt;/a&gt; at CP doctoral program.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;files/slides/fmcad21.pdf&#34;&gt;Designing sampler is easy: the boon of testers &lt;/a&gt; at Model counting workshop.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;files/publications/cp22_shakuni.pdf&#34;&gt;On quantitative testing of sampler &lt;/a&gt; at CP 2022.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;  &lt;a href=&#34;files/publications/cav-22-entropy.pdf&#34;&gt;A scalable Shannon entropy estimator &lt;/a&gt; at CAV 2022.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</title>
      <link>/talk/01082022/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Aug 2022 13:15:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>/talk/01082022/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Happy to present first in-person tutorial :)  We will be talking about &lt;a href=&#34;ijcai22-tutorial/index.html&#34;&gt;automated synthesis&lt;/a&gt; at IJCAI-22. </title>
      <link>/talk/24072022/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Jul 2022 14:15:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>/talk/24072022/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I am attending &lt;a href=&#34;https://highlights-conference.org/2022/&#34;&gt;Highlights of Logic, Games and Automata&lt;/a&gt;. I will be talking about our work on program synthesis as dependency quantified formulas.  Also, looking forward to visit Pierre Marquis and Daniel Le Berre as a part of Highlights Extended Stay Program.</title>
      <link>/talk/27062022/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jun 2022 14:15:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>/talk/27062022/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I am visiting Simons institute to attend the reunion for &lt;a href=&#34;https://simons.berkeley.edu/programs/sat2021&#34;&gt;Satisfiability: Theory, Practice, and Beyond &lt;/a&gt; program. I will be presenting our work on program synthesis as dependency quantified formulas. </title>
      <link>/talk/13062022/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2022 14:15:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>/talk/13062022/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>&lt;b&gt;Our work on A Scalable Shannon Entropy Estimator is accepted to  &lt;a href=&#34;http://i-cav.org/2022/&#34;&gt;CAV-22&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br&gt; We propose the first efficient algorithmic technique to estimate the Shannon entropy of a specification with PAC-style guarantees, i.e., the computed estimate is guaranteed to lie within a (1 ± ε)-factor of the ground truth with confidence &gt;= 1−δ. &lt;br&gt; Joint work with: Brendan Juba and Kuldeep S. Meel&lt;br&gt; </title>
      <link>/talk/09052022/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 May 2022 13:15:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>/talk/09052022/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Scalable Shannon Entropy Estimator</title>
      <link>/publication/cav22/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/publication/cav22/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>On Quantitative Testing of Samplers</title>
      <link>/publication/cp22/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/publication/cp22/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>&lt;b&gt;Our work On Quantitative Testing of Samplers has been accepted to  &lt;a href=&#34;https://cp2022.a4cp.org&#34;&gt;CP-22&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br&gt; We design a computational hardness-based tester, called ScalBarbarik. ScalBarbarik provides a qunatitative way to analysis the quality of a sampler.&lt;br&gt; Joint work with: Mate Soos, Sourav Chakraborty, Kuldeep S. Meel&lt;br&gt; </title>
      <link>/talk/08052022/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 May 2022 13:15:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>/talk/08052022/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Manthan</title>
      <link>/project/manthan/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/project/manthan/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Boolean functional synthesis is a fundamental problem in computer science with wide-ranging applications and has witnessed a surge of interest resulting in progressively improved techniques over the past decade. Despite intense algorithmic development, a large number of problems remain beyond the reach of the state of the art techniques. Motivated by the progress in machine learning, we propose Manthan, a novel data-driven approach to Boolean functional synthesis. Manthan views functional synthesis as a classification problem, relying on advances in constrained sampling for data generation, and advances in automated reasoning for a novel proof-guided refinement and provable verification.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Manthan significantly improves upon the current state of the art, solving 356 benchmarks in comparison to 280, which is the most solved by a state of the art technique; thereby, it demonstrate an increase of 76 benchmarks over the current state of the art. Furthermore, Manthan solves 60 benchmarks that none of the current state of the art techniques could solve.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Scalbarbarik</title>
      <link>/project/scalbarbarik/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/project/scalbarbarik/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The problem of uniform sampling is, given a formula F, sample solutions of F uniformly atrandom from the solution space of F. Uniform sampling is a fundamental problem with widespread applications, including configuration testing, bug synthesis, function synthesis, and many more. State-of-the-art approaches for uniform sampling have a trade-off between scalability and theoretical guarantees. Many state of the art uniform samplers do not provide any theoretical guarantees on the distribution of samples generated, however, empirically they have shown promising results. In such cases, the main challenge is to test whether the distribution according to which samples are generated is indeed uniform or not.
Recently, Chakraborty and Meel (2019) designed the first scalable sampling tester, Barbarik, based on a grey-box sampling technique for testing if the distribution, according to which the given sampler is sampling, is close to the uniform or far from uniform. They were able to show that many off-the-self samplers are far from a uniform sampler. The availability of Barbarik increased the test-driven development of samplers. More recently, Golia, Soos, Chakraborty and Meel (2021), designed a uniform like sampler, CMSGen, which was shown to be accepted by Barbarik on all the instances. However, CMSGen does not provide any theoretical analysis of the sampling quality. CMSGen leads us to observe the need for a tester to provide a quantitative answer to determine the quality of underlying samplers instead of merely a qualitative answer of Accept or Reject. Towards this goal, we design a computational hardness-based tester ScalBarbarik that provides a more nuanced analysis of the quality of a sampler. ScalBarbarik allows more expressive measurement of the quality of the underlying samplers. We empirically show that the state-of-the-art sampler, CMSGen is not accepted as a uniform-like sampler by ScalBarbarik. Furthermore, we show that ScalBarbarik can be used to design a sampler that can achieve balance between scalability and uniformity.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DeQuS</title>
      <link>/project/dequs/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/project/dequs/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Given a specification φ(X, Y ) over inputs X and output Y , defined over a background theory T, the problem of program synthesis is to design a program f such that Y = f (X) satisfies the specification φ. Over the past decade, syntax-guided synthesis (SyGuS) has emerged as a dominant approach to program synthesis where in addition to the specification φ, the end-user also specifies a grammar L to aid the underlying synthesis engine. This paper investigates the feasibility of synthesis techniques without grammar, a sub-class defined as T-constrained synthesis. 
We show that T-constrained synthesis can be reduced DQF(T), i.e., to the problem of finding a witness of a dependency quantified formula modulo theory. When the underlying theory is bitvectors, the corresponding DQF problem can be further reduced to Dependency Quantified Boolean Formulas (DQBF). We rely on the progress in DQBF solving to design DQBF-based synthesizers that outpeform the domain-specific program synthesis techniques, thereby positioning DQBF as a core representation language for program synthesis. Our empirical analysis shows that T-constrained synthesis can achieve significantly better scalability than syntax-guided approaches. Furthermore, the general purpose DQBF solvers perform on par with domain-specific synthesis techniques.
DeQuS takes a program synthesis instances and reduce it to a DQF(T) instance. Currenlty, DeQUS can only handle bitvector theory.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>EntropyEstimation</title>
      <link>/project/entropyestimation/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/project/entropyestimation/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Quantified information flow (QIF) has emerged as a rigorous approach to quantitatively measure confidentiality; the information-theoretic underpinning of QIF allows the end-users to link the computed quantities with the computational effort required on the part of the adversary to gain access to desired confidential information. In this work, we focus on the estimation of Shannon entropy for a given program Π. As a first step, we focus on the case wherein a Boolean formula φ(X, Y ) captures the relationship between inputs X and output Y of Π. Such formulas φ(X, Y ) have the property that for every valuation to X, there exists exactly one valuation to Y such that φ is satisfied. The existing techniques require O(2^m ) model counting queries, where m = |Y |. 
We propose the first efficient algorithmic technique, called EntropyEstimation to estimate the Shannon entropy of φ with PAC-style guarantees, i.e., the computed estimate is guaranteed to lie within a (1 ± ε)-factor of the ground truth with confidence at least 1−δ. Furthermore, EntropyEstimation makes only O( min(m,n)) counting and sampling queries, where m = |Y |, and n = |X|, thereby achieving a significant reduction in the number of model counting queries. We demonstrate the practical efficiency of our algorithmic framework via a detailed experimental evaluation. Our evaluation demonstrates that the proposed framework scales to the formulas beyond the reach of the previously known approaches.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>&lt;b&gt;Join, from the comfort of your home, our tutorial on &lt;a href=&#34;https://priyanka-golia.github.io/ijcai22-tutorial/index.html&#34;&gt;Automated Synthesis: Towards the Holy Grail of AI&lt;/a&gt; at AAAI-22.&lt;/b&gt;</title>
      <link>/talk/08012021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Jan 2022 14:15:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>/talk/08012021/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I will be giving a &lt;b&gt;student invited talk &lt;/b&gt; at &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.tifr.res.in/~shibashis.guha/iVerif/&#34;&gt;iVerif: Workshop on artifical intelligence and Verification &lt;/a&gt;. Its a pre-FSTTCS workshop. See you all at FSTTCS!</title>
      <link>/talk/12012021/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Dec 2021 14:15:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>/talk/12012021/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>&lt;b&gt;Our paper on Engineering an Efficient Boolean Functional Synthesis Engine has received the best paper nomination at ICCAD 21&lt;/b&gt;</title>
      <link>/talk/29082021/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Oct 2021 14:15:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>/talk/29082021/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I will be visiting Daniel Neider (MPI-SWS), Armin Biere (University of Freiburg) in two weeks from now!  Hoping to visit CISPA as well to meet Bernd Finkbeiner.</title>
      <link>/talk/01102021/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Oct 2021 13:15:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>/talk/01102021/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>&lt;b&gt;Our paper Engineering an Efficient Boolean Functional Synthesis Engine has been accepted to &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.iccad.com/index.php&#34;&gt;ICCAD 2021&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br&gt; The work addresses scalability barriers faced by the current state-of-the-art synthesis techniques. We propose four algorithmic improvements for a data-driven framework for functional synthesis.&lt;br&gt; Joint work with: Friedrich Slivovsky, Subhajit Roy and Kuldeep S. Meel&lt;br&gt; </title>
      <link>/talk/14072021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Aug 2021 13:15:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>/talk/14072021/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Engineering an Efficient Boolean Functional Synthesis Engine</title>
      <link>/publication/iccad21/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/publication/iccad21/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>&lt;b&gt;Our paper Designing Samplers is Easy: The Boon of Testers has been accepted to &lt;a href=&#34;https://fmcad.org/FMCAD21/&#34;&gt;FMCAD 2021&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br&gt; Our Sampler not only passes the tests of Barbarik but also leads to significant performance improvements for real-world instances. &lt;br&gt; Joint work with: Mate Soos, Sourav Chakraborty, Kuldeep S. Meel&lt;br&gt; </title>
      <link>/talk/09072021/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jul 2021 14:15:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>/talk/09072021/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Designing Samplers is Easy: The Boon of Testers</title>
      <link>/publication/fmcad21/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/publication/fmcad21/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CMSGen</title>
      <link>/project/cmsgen/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/project/cmsgen/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Given a formula the problem of uniform sampling seeks to sample solutions of uniformly at random. Uniform sampling is a fundamental problem with a wide variety of applications. The computational intractability of uniform sampling has led to the development of several samplers that heavily rely on heuristics and are not accompanied by theoretical analysis of their distribution. Recently, Chakraborty and Meel (2019) designed the first scalable sampling tester, Barbarik, based on a grey-box sampling technique for testing if the distribution, according to which the given sampler is sampling, is close to the uniform or far from uniform. While the theoretical analysis of Barbarik provides only unconditional soundness guarantees, the empirical evaluation of Barbarik did show its success in determining that some of the off-the-shelf samplers were far from a uniform sampler.
The availability of Barbarik has the potential to spur development of samplers and testing techniques such that developers can design sampling methods that can be accepted by Barbarik even though these samplers may not be amenable to a detailed mathematical analysis. In this paper, we present the realization of this aforementioned promise. Based on the flexibility offered by CryptoMiniSat, we design a sampler CMSGen that promises the achievement of sweet spot of the quality of distributions and runtime performance. In particular, CMSGen achieves significant runtime performance improvement over the existing samplers. We conduct two case studies, and demonstrate that the usage of CMSGen leads to significant runtime improvements in the context of combinatorial testing and functional synthesis.
A salient strength of our work is the simplicity of CMSGen, which stands in contrast to complicated algorithmic schemes developed in the past that fail to attain desired quality of distributions with practical runtime performance.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>&lt;b&gt;Excited to announce that I will presenting a talk on synthesis at the &lt;a href=&#34;https://esslli2021.unibz.it/&#34;&gt;32nd, European Summer School in  Logic, Language, and Information&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/b&gt;</title>
      <link>/talk/29072021/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jul 2021 14:15:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>/talk/29072021/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Henkin Synthesis: DQBF meets Machine Learning</title>
      <link>/publication/logic-workshop/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jul 2021 01:06:16 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>/publication/logic-workshop/</guid>
      <description>&lt;hr&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Henkin Synthesis: DQBF meets Machine Learning</title>
      <link>/workshop/logic-workshop/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jul 2021 01:06:16 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>/workshop/logic-workshop/</guid>
      <description>&lt;hr&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Manthan: A Data-Driven Approach for Boolean Function Synthesis</title>
      <link>/publication/essli-workshop/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jul 2021 01:06:16 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>/publication/essli-workshop/</guid>
      <description>&lt;hr&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Manthan: A Data-Driven Approach for Boolean Function Synthesis</title>
      <link>/workshop/essli-workshop/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jul 2021 01:06:16 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>/workshop/essli-workshop/</guid>
      <description>&lt;hr&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Program Synthesis as Dependency Quantified Formula Modulo Theory</title>
      <link>/publication/qbf-workshop/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jul 2021 01:06:16 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>/publication/qbf-workshop/</guid>
      <description>&lt;hr&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Program Synthesis as Dependency Quantified Formula Modulo Theory</title>
      <link>/workshop/qbf-workshop/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jul 2021 01:06:16 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>/workshop/qbf-workshop/</guid>
      <description>&lt;hr&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>&lt;b&gt;Our paper on Program Synthesis as Dependency Quantified Formula Modulo Theory has been accepted to &lt;a href=&#34;https://ijcai-21.org/&#34;&gt;IJCAI 2021&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br&gt;We show that theory-constrained synthesis can be reduced DQF(T), i.e., to the problem of finding a witness of a dependency quantified formula modulo theory. &lt;br&gt; Joint work with: Subhajit Roy and Kuldeep S. Meel&lt;br&gt; </title>
      <link>/talk/30042021/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Apr 2021 14:15:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>/talk/30042021/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Program Synthesis as Dependency Quantified Formula Modulo Theory</title>
      <link>/publication/ijcai21/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/publication/ijcai21/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>We presented a data-driven approach for [Boolean functional synthesis](https://www.comp.nus.edu.sg/~meel/Papers/cav20-grm.pdf), which works at the intersection of constrained sampling, machine learning and automated reasoning at [CAV 2020](http://i-cav.org/2020/).</title>
      <link>/talk/22072020/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>/talk/22072020/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>&lt;b&gt;Presented a talk on a data driven approach for Boolean function synthesis at 4th Workshop on Learning in Verification (LiVe), ETPAS, 2020 and at Software Engineering Research in India, SERI, 2020&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/b&gt;</title>
      <link>/talk/15072020/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jul 2020 14:15:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>/talk/15072020/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Manthan: A Data-Driven Approach for Boolean Function Synthesis</title>
      <link>/publication/cav20-manthan/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/publication/cav20-manthan/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>&lt;b&gt;We have released the source code of [Manthan](https://github.com/meelgroup/manthan).&lt;/b&gt;</title>
      <link>/talk/04072020/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>/talk/04072020/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Data-Driven Approach for Skolem Function Synthesis</title>
      <link>/publication/live-tacas-20-manthan/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Apr 2020 01:06:16 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>/publication/live-tacas-20-manthan/</guid>
      <description>&lt;hr&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Data-Driven Approach for Skolem Function Synthesis</title>
      <link>/workshop/live-tacas-20-manthan/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Apr 2020 01:06:16 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>/workshop/live-tacas-20-manthan/</guid>
      <description>&lt;hr&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>&lt;b&gt;Our paper on A data-driven approach for Boolean function synthesis has been accepted to CAV-20&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt; Joint work with: Subhajit Roy and Kuldeep S. Meel</title>
      <link>/talk/07072020/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>/talk/07072020/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
