<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Priyanka</title>
    <link>/</link>
      <atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>Priyanka</description>
    <generator>Source Themes Academic (https://sourcethemes.com/academic/)</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 19 May 2020 01:06:16 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    <image>
      <url>/images/icon_hu0b7a4cb9992c9ac0e91bd28ffd38dd00_9727_512x512_fill_lanczos_center_2.png</url>
      <title>Priyanka</title>
      <link>/</link>
    </image>
    
    <item>
      <title>Manthan: A Data-Driven Approach for Boolean Function Synthesis</title>
      <link>/publication/cav20-manthan/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 May 2020 01:06:16 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>/publication/cav20-manthan/</guid>
      <description>&lt;hr&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Data-Driven Approach for Skolem Function Synthesis</title>
      <link>/publication/live-tacas-20-manthan/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Apr 2020 01:06:16 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>/publication/live-tacas-20-manthan/</guid>
      <description>&lt;hr&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Manthan</title>
      <link>/project/manthan/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/project/manthan/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Boolean functional synthesis is a fundamental problem in computer science with wide-ranging applications and has witnessed a surge of interest resulting in progressively improved techniques over the past decade. Despite intense algorithmic development, a large number of problems remain beyond the reach of the state of the art techniques. Motivated by the progress in machine learning, we propose Manthan, a novel data-driven approach to Boolean functional synthesis. Manthan views functional synthesis as a classification problem, relying on advances in constrained sampling for data generation, and advances in automated reasoning for a novel proof-guided refinement and provable verification.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Manthan significantly improves upon the current state of the art, solving 356 benchmarks in comparison to 280, which is the most solved by a state of the art technique; thereby, it demonstrate an increase of 76 benchmarks over the current state of the art. Furthermore, Manthan solves 60 benchmarks that none of the current state of the art techniques could solve.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
